Workers United Publications 6284 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United Publications
1996-2013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6284 PUBS
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
8822495
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 03, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Workers United
8822495
- The 14th Street Tribune (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 25th Anniversary Local 91 ILGWU, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 25th Anniversary of the Presidency of David Dubinsky and ILGWU Progress, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 61st Annual Hillman Prizes in Journalism, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 146 Dead in Triangle Fire, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The 1199/Employer Child Care Fund Local Committee Manual (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Acting 2: Collaboration: The Legacy of the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire (2011) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Advocate's Guide to IRCA Employment Discrimination, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- America's War on Poverty (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bienvenidos a UNITE (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Scope and Contents
  Spanish
- Anti-Sweatshop, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bread and Roses Project (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Breaking Ground, Breaking Silence (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A Brief History of the International Ladies' Garment Worker's Union (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Building Connections, Creating Communities (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CAFTA and Free Trade (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chinatown Manpower Project, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chinese Women in the Garment Industry (Box 1, Folder 18)
- The Clara Lemlich Awards (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Collect Bargaining Agreement, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Creative Expressions, 2002-2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- English in the Garment Shops (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fiscal Policy Institute, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Forum, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- From the Fire, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Garment Industry Development Center (Box 1, Folder 26)
- The Garment Industry in New York City (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Garment Workers' Center Workplace Literacy Class, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  English and Chinese. Summer 1995
- Greater Blouse, Skirt and Undergarments Association, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- High Fashion; High Tech; High Skill (Box 1, Folder 30)
- History of the Sewing Machine - James Parton, 1867 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- ILGWU News-History 1990-1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Photocopy, reduced size. The actual copy of this publication will not fit in this box. For the full-size, as-published, copy see: Collection Number: 6046 Box 703;ff 4.
- ILGWU Report and Record, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- The ILGWU Song Book, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- ILGWU Union Health Center Celebrating 75 Years of Service, 1914-1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- I'm Entitled, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Immigrant Women: Their Untold History - Joyce Scane and Marjatta Holt (1988) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- It's in Your Hands, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- The Italian-American Labor Council (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Japan Labor Review Vol. 7 No. 1, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Joint Responsibility Bill (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Keeping New York in Fashion, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Labor and the Arts, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Labor Celebration and Gala Dinner Dance, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- The Literacy Review, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Volume 10 (2012) and volume 11 (2013).
- Local 23-25: A Union of Firsts (Box 1, Folder 46)
- The Magnet, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  v.2:no.1 (1999:Spring)
- Make a Difference (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Memories: A Bridge from the Past to the Present, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Naturalization Interview (Box 1, Folder 50)
- New Labor Forum: The Legacy of the Triangle Fire, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- New York City: Our City, Our Union, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- The New York State Citizenship Campaign (Box 2, Folder 1)
- News Clippings (Box 2, Folder 2)
- No FTAA (Box 2, Folder 3)
- No Freedom Without Privacy, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- No Sweat, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- One Vision, One Voice, One Moment, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Organized Labor: Source Materials for the Study of Labor in America (1991) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Pa'a Hui Unions 1966-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Pauline Newman, 1893-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Posesi de los Miembros (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Poetry from ESL Class with Garment Workers (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Poetry Unit (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Proudly Made in New York (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Ralph Fasanella, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Real Estate, 2000-2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Remember the Triangle Fire Location (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Repetitive Strain Injuries, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- The Rights of Aliens, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Shop Conditions (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Shop Representative Training Materials (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Skills for Tomorrow (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Still Climbing Up the Rough Side of the Mountain, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Sweatfree Purchasing Consortium (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Sweatshop: An Exhibition by New York City Public School Students, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- They are Not Forgotten, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- The Triangle Factory Fire Project, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Triangle Fire Open Museum (Box 2, Folder 30)
- The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire, March 25, 1911, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Uniform Justice, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Union Basics: ESL Lessons (Box 2, Folder 33)
  ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program
- Union Predicts Company Tricks (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Unite! Vol. 2 No. 5 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Unite! Basic Steward Training Manual (Box 2, Folder 36)
- UNIE / Chinatown Level I Curriculum (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Unite! Constitution, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Unite! Fight Size, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- UNITE! Mission Statement (Box 2, Folder 40)
- UNITE New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  v.1:no.1 (2004:Spring/Summer)
- Unite! Political Action Handouts (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Unite! Song Book (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Unite! Stewards' Handbook (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Unite Here Constitution, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Unity House ILGWU (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Unseen America, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Voices Magazine, 198-1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Weeding Out Abuses, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- What's In A Name, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  UNITE! Worker Education Program. February 1996
- Women in the Global Economy (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Women of Hope Study Guide, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Workers United (Box 2, Folder 53)